https://www.circomedia.com/circomedia-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Circomedia is committed to protecting your personal information and being transparent about what information we hold on you. We use your personal data to provide our services to you. In particular, we will use the information we hold about you to:
Provide educational and support services to our students and staff
Provide commercial activities to our customers and hirers
Advertise and promote the services we offer
Publish newsletters and maintain alumni relations
Undertake research and fundraising
Manage our accounts and legal records
Use CCTV to protect our premises
It allows us to develop a better understanding of you and in turn provide you with relevant and timely information about the work that we do – both on stage and off stage. As a charity, it also helps us engage with potential donors and supporters.
When we talk about data and personal data in this policy, we mean personal data which identify you or which could be used to identify you such as your name and contact details. It might also be your academic record or your booking details for shows and classes. It may also include information about how you use our website and mobile applications.
We have described how we collect, store and use your data in this Privacy Policy. There are steps you can take to control what we do with your data and this policy will explain your rights and the actions you can take. Under current legislation we are not obliged to employ a Data Protection Officer however, we have internal policies and procedures to govern the way we respond to your data requests and any changes to your preferences regarding the way we use your personal data.
If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us at info@circomedia.com or you can write to us at Circomedia, Kingswood Foundation, Britannia Road, Kingswood, Bristol, BS15 8DB.
Download the full privacy policy
Share this page
